Here we go... Upokami!
This time with Ami Tanimoto of Tsubaki Factory
and Mari Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory.
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists
We'll be going behind the scenes of the production of the various artists who belong to the Upfrant Group.
our recordings and rehearsals.
We will show you the behind-the-scenes of our recording and rehearsal process.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at our two MCs.
I, Tanimoto, would like to talk about Tsubaki Factory's major debut 7th anniversary live performance "Rear-Eyez" that was held the other day.
We had a shorter rehearsal period than usual for this live performance.
We had a very short rehearsal period.
So, during the rehearsals, there were quite a few new doubled values scattered around.
We had to learn a lot of new songs with new double values scattered throughout the songs.
It was really hard, and when we were rehearsing, I would suddenly think, "There's the next double value," or "There's the next double value," or "There's the next double value.
Where was it?
I'm like, "Oh, where is it?
When I was fidgeting, Mari Fukuda was helping me with the doubling of the value, and she would help me by helping me with her hand, like, "This way, Tanimoto-san, this way," and I thought that Mari was getting more and more fun.
Thank you very much.
And I, Fukuda
Yes
Recently, in order to strengthen my singing
To strengthen my abdominal muscles
Wow, that's great
I think most people start strength training for dancing or for physical fitness, but my voice training teacher told me that if I strengthen my abdominal muscles, I will be able to produce a higher and more stable temperature.
My voice training instructor told me that if I strengthened my abdominal muscles, I would be able to produce a stable high temperature.
That's great!
But if I notice it...
I hope she does!
Recently, Tsubaki Factory members
Quite a lot.
I'm sure.
Everyone
Yes...
Many of them have started muscle training.
I've been invited by Okinawa and Akihabara and Saori Onoda.
They told me to do it with them, so I've been doing it during the time between performances.
But it's good, because I can strengthen my performance by doing muscle training.
I hope you will pay a lot of attention to Tsubaki Factory's performance from now on.
Now, let's start with the uploads of this time.
Rei Inoue's makeup lesson
This is a makeup lecture by Rei Inoue of JuiceJuice.
What kind of makeup will she be showing us?
I'm Rui Inoue from JuiceJuice. Today, I've been getting a lot of requests from my fans about how I do my makeup.
I've been getting a lot of questions lately about eyelashes, so I'd like to give a makeup lecture focusing on the root area.
Overall, I've been emphasizing blood color.
That's why my blush is a little darker than others.
Now I have concealer on.
I use this one. I like the smell of this one the best.
I like the Maria Jasmine scent the best.
Even if you don't usually wear makeup, you should try this powder.
I don't like to put it on before going to bed.
Even if you don't like powdery makeup, you can use it.
I have thick eyebrows, so I just put on some eyebrow mascara and apply it today.
I always decide the look of today's makeup by applying eyebrow mascara.
I'm not particular about eyebrow mascara, I just try not to get it on my skin.
I just do it quickly so that it doesn't get on my skin.
That's how I feel about it.
When it comes to face shadow, I still don't know much about it.
I don't know much about face shadows yet.
I'm already doing a lot around this area of the face.
I'm doing it in a very relaxed way.
I might put the nose shadow firmly in my eyes.
I think it makes me look more mature.
I put a lot here.
Here.
I have it here, but not so much here, so I put a little bit here and here. I'm a big fan of upnose, so I put it here too.
I'm a big fan of the upnose, so I'll put a little bit more shadow here and a little bit more there.
I put a little bit of shadow here and there, and then I put a little bit of shadow around the tip of the nose.
I've been applying blush along with my eye shadow lately, so I've been using the same color as my eye shadow.
I'm a blue-ish person, so I'm going to use a slightly dull orange rather than a bright orange range.
I put it under my eyes.
I apply it horizontally rather than vertically, from under the dark eye to the bottom of the cheekbone.
I apply it from the bottom of the dark eye to the most prominent part of the cheekbone.
Then I'll put it in here, too, and then I'll put it on the tip of the nose, just a little bit, just a little bit.
In winter, when it's cold, the nose turns red.
I think it's cute when a girl's nose turns red in the winter when it's cold, but if you put too much of this around the nose, it makes the nose look kind of hot.
I like to put a little bit of this around the nose too.
I like to put a little bit of this around the nose and chin as well.
If you start from the outside of the eyehall, you'll end up with a sharp border.
I've been using a lot of different colors lately.
The first thing to do is to apply the same color to the entire eyehall.
If you want a more powerful face, you may want to use a darker color for the tear ducts.
I think you can use any color you like for the tear ducts.
I think it would be good if you extend it a little with your fingers. See you in the next video!
Trace and Blur
Trace and blur
If you do this, your tear troughs will be born!
The key point for me is to draw eyebrows.
I use an eyebrow pencil.
I put a little bit here.
I put it in and blur it out again.
After that, use a thin brush.
I couldn't find a very thin one.
I also use this one.
If you trace a little bit of the color you used for this eyeshadow
I trace a little bit of the color I used for this eyeshadow
I always do it because I think it looks cute.
This is how I made my tear troughs.
When I perform live, I tend to put a lot of lame here.
I usually put a lot of lame here.
But this time, I didn't use such a large amount of lame.
I was thinking of doing it this time.
I took a brush that was a little smaller than the one I used before.
Take a smaller brush and put a little bit of the same color as here.
Take a little bit of this color of the rainbow.
Put it in this triangular zone.
I want the width.
I have rather round eyes.
That's the kind of eyes you like.
I like this kind of eye better.
I'm going to extend it horizontally.
I'm going to finish the shadow.
I'll add and subtract when I'm done again.
I'm going to add and subtract.
I've been getting a lot of questions
I've been getting a lot of questions.
I've been getting a lot of questions about my eyelashes.
I'm not doing anything with them right now.
I usually use orange or black.
I'm always torn between the two.
I usually use the black one.
I use black when I don't have a lot of eyeshadow.
I use it a lot.
If I use brown, it gives a gentler look.
Along with that
Prepare tweezers.
I'm going to make a bunch of hair.
Bundles? Bundles? Bundle?
I mean...
When you apply mascara, it's really...
It's fine if you don't mind.
Just put some liquid on your lashes.
Just put it on your lashes.
It's fine.
Just pinch a little bit to get the lashes to the size you want.
Just pinch a little bit.
and you're good to go.
If you start from the eyes
If you start from the eyes, you'll end up with too many bunches.
I don't like it.
Just the tip.
Pinch it like this.
Some people do it very beautifully.
I'm not so sure.
I don't like it so much.
I tend to look at it from a distance.
I've never seen it at such a close distance.
It's about the time when I'm guessing my makeup.
This is more rough.
Some people use four strands here, or a bunch there.
Some people have a bunch of hair here and there.
It's a little bit more natural.
So it's really up to you.
The other day, I saw a member's
eyelashes and the whole makeup
I had to do their eyelashes and overall makeup.
It was totally different.
I think it really depends on the person.
It was difficult to get a sense of what would look best on each person.
It was difficult to find the right bunching that suited me.
So please do your research!
And the lower lashes.
This is really just a touch of influence.
After raising the lashes, fine-tune them with tweezers.
It's not about creating a beautiful bunch.
It's more like scattering them in a well-balanced way.
I do it with a sense of balance.
This is how I do my lashes.
When I draw eyeliner, I do it like this.
If I draw it like this, it looks too harsh.
It makes my eyes look bad.
So I just draw eyeliner on the corner of my eyes.
I always draw eyeliner like this.
Like this!
Please look forward to the next video!
If you want a little more definition, you can draw eyeliner over the dark eye and it won't make much difference.
It doesn't have to be that much different.
It will be a little different, but it won't look like you're wearing a lot of eyeliner.
That's what I recommend.
Lastly, my life! More important than bangs! Lips!
I like dull colors, so I only have dull colors.
My latest craze is the tulle lip!
It's done!
First of all, I wanted to create a sense of blood color.
I wanted to create a sense of unity in the blood coloring.
I used the same color for eyeshadow here, here, here, and here.
You can add more if you like.
For the eyelashes, we did not bunch the lashes from the root.
Only the tips of the lashes should be like this.
We're going to bunch the lashes so that they look like this.
Don't draw a line all the way down, just at the corner of the eye.
I've been doing this every day lately.
I'm sure you'll all be able to use this as a reference and become pretty too!
I'm sure I'll be doing a lot more makeup in the future.
I'm sure I'll be doing a lot more makeup in the future, so I hope you'll take note of it when you look at my photos.
This is Rui Inoue.
Thank you very much.
We've looked at the makeup of Rui Inoue, a teacher woman.
Lovely!
Cute!
She was cute!
Yes, yes...
He's my favorite.
It's not easy.
I've never seen you like this.
You don't get to see her like this all the time.
I was really happy.
But you know...
Rui studied a lot about makeup.
Even though you're already so cute.
It's amazing.
She researches her makeup so much.
I thought it was amazing.
It's the latest makeup.
But at concerts.
You wear several outfits, right?
That's right.
So if you're wearing pink at first...
I'll wear a pink lipstick, too.
And after changing, if the costume is a little reddish...
I would take off the lipstick and put on a reddish lipstick.
and put on a reddish lip.
It's great.
You try to change it up.
I'm not very good at makeup.
I recently received a pink and gold
I got a pink and gold eyebrow mascara.
I'm wearing the pink one today.
I'm wearing the pink one.
I've been wearing the same kind of makeup
I've always worn the same kind of makeup.
I've been wearing the same kind of makeup for a long time, so I've been wearing pinkish makeup recently.
I've been trying to wear pinkish makeup
I've been trying to do a little bit of research
I've started to think that I'd like to do a little research
I've started to think about it, and I did my best today.
I was able to learn about Inoue-san's obsession with makeup as well.
I learned a lot from Inoue-san's makeup, and I'll be doing it when I do my makeup from now on.
I learned a lot from Inoue-san's makeup and I'm going to use it as a reference when I do my own makeup.
I hope I can use your makeup as a reference when I do my own makeup in the future.
That was the makeup lecture by Rei Inoue of Juice Juice.
Cheer up!
Next, here we go!
Tsubaki Factory Power Flower: Now is the Time to be an Eye - Vocal Recording
We recorded the vocals for the song "Power Flower" from Tsubaki Factory's latest album.
Please check out the vocal recording of Shiori Yagi from "Power Flower, Now is the Time to be an Eye"!
Okay, there are a lot of blocks.
Let's start with the first A melody.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
The signal for the beginning... the modest light... the modest soprin... but the hidden pride... the red blooming city... the solid no city...
Red city, red city, hard city, no city, strikingly bright, strikingly vivid, strikingly vivid
It's a city that stands out, it's a city that stands out, it's a city that stands out.
If you sing "eye-catching" too much, you won't get the bounce.
I'm gonna be eye-catching, I'm gonna be eye-catching, I'm gonna be eye-catching
It's eye-catching, it's eye-catching, it's eye-catching, it's eye-catching.
It's a little abbreviated.
"Eye-catching, eye-catching, eye-catching, eye-catching, eye-catching.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. That's how it's going to be.
Silent as a cue to begin
A modest sled, but with hidden pride
Red blooming fighting spirit, brought back tight
Eye-catching and vivid.
Yeah, it's perfect.
Let's move on to the next one.
Okay, I'm going to split it in two.
Okay, take one.
Take 1: Idol Song
2 Whole body density
3, all go out, all go out, spirit go out.
4 Time is Melky, Time is Vivid
5 All Departure Spirit Departure
Everything gonna be alright
Okay, then, the other one.
Time to be melky, time to be brilliant.
All hands on deck. We're gathering now.
Spirit out. You know what I'm talking about, you got that look in your eye.
Showtime to jump on the bandwagon and raise the juli-juli-juli-juli-juli-juli-vibrator.
Unexplored by all, here we come!
Everything gonna be alright
Camellia, hanami, underground monkey, everything!
Why are you tilting your head?
I thought it would be difficult
I'm not sure I'm in the mood for a get-together
We're getting together now.
Yeah, that's about right.
Time is a thing of beauty, and it's time to make it a thing of beauty.
All hands on deck. We're gathering now.
♪ Spirit, you know what I'm talking about, you got that look in your eye
Showtime to jump on the two-handed bandwagon and raise the julijuli-juli-juli-vibrator
Unexplored by all, here we come!
Everything gonna be alright
Camellia, hanami, underground monkey, everything!
Right hand
Looks rushed
The intensity
Like a conductor.
Okay, let's go with that.
Okay, let's try this next one.
Camellias, hanami, underground monkeys... everything's fine.
Everything is fine
The overlapping forces
The overlapping forces face the blue sky
The figure is dignified and beautiful
graceful and beautiful all over the world
First of all, my head went in a little too hard.
And I'd like to guess the pitch of the "Rin" designation a little more.
Let's try one more time with
Camellias, hanami, underground monkeys, every single thing
everything is fine
The overlapping forces are heading for the blue sky
The figure is dignified, graceful, and beautiful all over the world
I'll take the first stroke
A little rhythmic awareness of overlapping forces
The overlapping power
The overlapping power...
Let's take another shot with a little awareness of that.
Camellias, hanami, underground monkeys, everything is fine.
Everything is fine
The overlapping forces are pointing towards the blue sky.
Okay, let's try the next one.
Camellia, Hanami, the colander, all in one piece.
Everything is fine.
Camellias, camellias, underground monkeys, all in one piece
Dreams to bloom all over the world
I can't choose them alone
I'll keep shining redder and redder on you
I still feel like I'm pushing too hard.
Let's relax a little and sing a little more
Yes, sir.
Small and beautiful
Camellias, hanami, underground monkeys, every last one of them
A dream to be cherished
I can't make them come true alone
I'll keep on shining redder and redder
about you.
Yeah, it's nice.
Next was the latter half of the chorus.
Very sharp.
Yes.
Let's try it then.
Keep shining the red light
You.
Now is the time to be one eye
Go forward with your feelings together
to a place you've never seen before.
Power Flower
Now is the time to be with one eye
Go forward with all your heart
To a place you've never seen before
Power Flower
Yeah, Power Flower was better in the second half.
A little shorter, power flower.
Do you pronounce this well?
power
power flower
If you're into it, that might be a good idea.
Keep shining the red light
about you.
Now is the time to be one eye
Feel together and move forward
to a place you've never seen before.
Power Flower
Now is the time to be with one eye
Go forward with all your heart
To a place you've never seen before
Power Flower
OK, let's move on.
Okay.
Okay, let's hear the 2A rap.
2A Wrap
Movement starting with 1, 2, 3.
If you meet a bumpy ride, you happen to be a fautin
Sitting down and transmitting
more curiosity matching than top
I'll put a little more boo in the movement
Movement begins with 1,2,3
movement
Movement
Movements beginning with 1,2,3
Bumpy and accidental meeting
CROACHING
Sitting down and transmitting
Curiosity over fear
Outay
Okay, okay.
Okay, second half.
meeting over bumpy surfaces is a coincidence
Croaching
Sitting down and transmitting
Curiosity over fear
Outie
Etch-a-Sketch turn is a movie
Painting tomorrow with determination
a personality that won't give up for a moment
I start to dance
The destination is clear
The correct answer
The rest of the dance is already underway
The character that doesn't give up for a moment
I'm going to start dancing
that's right!
I'm going to take out your personality.
It's like, "I'm gonna take out your personality.
I'll take out the personality.
Yeah.
Then you're probably not going to make it.
Okay.
It's just a coincidence that we meet on a bumpy road.
Croaching
Sitting down and sending a message
more curiosity than fear
Outay
Etch-a-Sketch turn is a movie
Painting tomorrow with determination
a personality that won't give up for a moment
I start to dance
The destination is clear
OK, we're done
Okay, we're done.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
This
Yes, sir.
This time, we have Yaggy Shun-chan's
I was watching the vocal recording
I was watching the recording of Yaggy Chun's vocal
This song has a lot of bass and treble
I had the impression that it was difficult to go back and forth between the low and high notes
I had the impression that the transition between the low and high notes was very difficult.
I thought the transition between the low and high notes was very smooth.
I think it's because I know my voice quality
I think it's because you know your voice quality and the pitches you can hit
and where to switch to the back voice...
Shiori Yagi herself knows how to switch to the back voice.
I could really get this feeling from the VTR.
about music.
I could feel the atmosphere of the music.
I also felt the atmosphere of the music.
And the rap part...
This time it was me, Ami Tanimoto and
and Shinnuma Kisora.
I was in charge of the rap part for this song.
When I saw Shiori-chan's recording of the song
I found it very interesting that she expressed herself in a different way from us
I thought it was very interesting.
I felt that it would be great if we could incorporate that kind of expression into our songs.
And you know what?
This song is an official Japan Hockey Association song for the Japan National Hockey Team Cheering Festival.
Yes, it is!
This song is for the Japan National Hockey Team Cheering Festival, officially approved by the Japan Hockey Association.
Yes, sir.
Good afternoon
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
I think there will be some music playing for the SLR and Nare.
I hope you will be interested in field hockey and look forward to this release.
Let's do it!
We hope that those who come to see the event with their own hockey sticks will be interested in the Tsubaki Factory.
I hope it will be an opportunity for those who come to see the event
I hope this will be a good opportunity for those who come to see the show with their own hockey sticks
I hope everyone will listen to the show and
I hope you will love it as much as I do.
That's all for now, Power Flower, let's be united as one!
This is Shiori Yanagi's vocal recording.
Take care of yourself and don't overdo it!
This is "Apkamin" by Ami Tanimoto of Tsubaki Factory and Marin Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory.
Here's the next one!
Morning Musume。23 wake up call Wake up when you wake up Vocal recording
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Rio Sakurai's vocal for Morning Musume。 23's latest single, "Wake Up Call: When You Wake Up".
Okay, let's get to it.
Yes, please.
I'll start with the A melody of the first number.
You don't look good in that makeup. It's an imposition of femininity that can't be erased.
I'm sorry, it's not for you. That's all I'm trying to say.
Just be careful not to go too low.
That's it.
Now that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right.
And now for the nuance.
I wanted to make you look a little more manly, a little more brusque.
You don't look good in that kind of makeup. It's an imposition of femininity that can't be removed.
Unfortunately, for you.
That's not what I'm trying to say.
I want to look a little more manly. Let's go again.
I'm begging you!
You don't look good in that makeup. It's an imposition of femininity that can't be erased.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I want to say.
Good. Let's go again.
Let's move on.
A multifaceted creature, a cootie-shootie-chewie...
I'll never leave it to others. I'll decide for myself.
I'll decide for myself, and I won't be fooled.
Wake up God
I am... I am...
I'm... I'm...
Maybe I know what the right answer is, but maybe I'm just a little overzealous and Sharpie-ish.
Sing it from the front
I can't shake this feeling I'll be fine
I'll sing it calmly and maybe it'll be okay
One more time
Please, I beg you
A multifaceted creature, any face is a cootie-shootie-shootie-shootie
I'm sure it's boring to leave it up to others I'll decide for myself, this thought is unshakable
I don't want to be fooled
Wake up God
I can't shake this thought that I decide for myself I don't want to be fooled Wake up God
I'm so crazy about you, such a creature, express what you feel.
Times are turning, happiness
It keeps changing, and I'm sure it will never change
Everyone has colorful possibilities
Wake up God
Yes, that's what it means
Because the rhythm of "Everybody" flows a little
I'm sure it will never change
Everyone has colorful possibilities
Yeah, let's be aware of that much, shall we?
Yes.
You're full of it, you're such a creature, express what you feel.
About стран
Times are turning toward happiness
It keeps changing, and it will never change
Everyone has colorful possibilities
Wake up God
Is the first line metal?
Yes, sir.
Times will turn
The times, they are turning.
The times they are a-spinning
Slow
You're late.
I'm sorry, I'm a little rusty.
I couldn't get into the rhythm at all.
Be careful there.
Yes, sir.
I felt like a creature who's lost in time.
I don't want to deceive you.
I don't want you to cheat me.
Wake up call It's time to wake up It's time to enjoy life
The sun is in my heart Just for you Just for you Just for you Just for you
I'll light up the dance
Rabbi dance Rabbi dance Rabbi dance Rabbi dance
Enjoying life is the part where the rhythm tends to drift a bit
Just for you Just for you Wake up call
It's time to enjoy life
The tempo is set by the way the "1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
Go up a notch or two! It's time to pack up the drums.
It's time to enjoy life.
Do it that way.
I don't want you to cheat on me.
WAKE UP CALL It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
The sun is in my heart
JUST DO IT, JUST DO IT, JUST DO IT, JUST DO IT!
I'll light up the dance
In the old place
At the bottom of the night
Then let's do it
Please do it
In the depths of the night
Someone's heart is waiting for morning, and I can get it.
Here in Korea, too, well, I'll wait for morning there, and hope I can make it.
In the depths of the night
Someone's heart waiting for morning I'll get it
Let's just say at the bottom of the night
At the bottom of the night
me
I'll take this, please.
I have to go through the process.
I have to go through the process... but I have to go through the process.
I love it... I love the creature with the "no problem"...
I'm sure you'll be able to get a good look at it, but this one has one special skill that would be great if you bought it.
It could be a weapon to extend the bottom part of the body.
A creature with many faces.
Okay, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much, that's it.
We've seen a video of Rio Sakurai recording her vocals.
I think this song is really hard work, going from low notes to high notes all at once, and it must be really hard to record.
I was impressed by the way Akebia-chan was able to absorb the advice from the director and change her voice as she went along, and I was also impressed by the way she was able to absorb it instantly and use it to her fullest potential.
The other day, we were on a concert tour with Morning Musume・24 and Beyoncé at a concert called "3 of us".
We were on a concert tour with Morning Musume 24 and the Beyons the other day, and this song
I felt from offstage that Aya's solo part was getting better and better with each new member, so I was really excited to hear the full version of this song this time.
So I was very happy to see her singing this song in full this time.
And as you can see from the lyrics of this song, it's quite a tribute to the old song.
It's a tribute to an old song.
Yes
There are some parts of the song that are a tribute to old songs
It's like a congrature or a revolution.
Revolution, etc.
I hope you will pay attention to the lyrics of this song and listen to it.
That's all for Morning Musume。 23' Make Up Call: Waking Up When You Wake Up was a vocal recording by Rio Sakurai.
Let's work together!
It's time for Ami Tanimoto and Marin Fukuda to say goodbye to Apkami!
We've seen a lot of different videos this time, too.
I, Fukuda, was very impressed by the vocal recording of Shiori Yagi and Rio Sakurai.
I was reminded once again that the difficulty of each Hello Project song is very different from each other.
I was also impressed by the way the two singers were sincerely working on the songs.
I felt the difficulty and hardship of the recording process again today.
I felt once again that I would like to be as earnest and focused as the two of them when I try to record in the future.
And I, Tanimoto, am taking a makeup class with Rei Inoue of JuiceJuice.
I've never had a chance to see my idol wearing makeup so closely.
And I'm sure there are a lot of fans or people who really want to know about her daily makeup.
I thought it was really wonderful to be able to see so many different makeup styles like this.
In APKAMI, we're going to take you behind the scenes to see what goes on behind the scenes with the various artists who belong to the UPFRONT GROUP.
We'll introduce you to the parts you don't usually get to see.
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time on Apkami, we'll be talking with Ami Tanimoto of Tsubaki Factory and
and Marin Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory.
Good bye.
Next time on Apkami, the recording of Tsubaki Factory's newest album
The recording of the third moment and
Juice Juice Wonderful World 2023 Recording of Juice Juice Version!
Enjoy!
That's it.